Suddenly Explorers
Uchiromiya, Mikinokono no Star Resto
Staff of Ikinari Talk
Pleased to meet you.
I'm whistling or not.
Thank you very much.
I'm Kannen Whistling. I'm from the Ikinari Expedition.
Today, I'd like you two to explore...
Coordinate your outfits at Spinz!
Spinz opened on the 2nd floor of Ebbins in April.
Speaking of Spinz, Tohoku-san came here too, right?
So I'd like to take you to Spinz to see how they coordinate their outfits.
Let's go to the store first!
Let's go!
We've arrived at the Spinz store!
It's so spacious!
Wow!
It's a lot bigger than I thought it would be.
Okay, first of all...
Before we get into the fashion showdown.
Let's take a look around the store
Let's take a look around.
First of all...
Men's, women's, used clothes...
And these are some miscellaneous goods.
I heard they sell all kinds of stuff.
You'll find everything you need.
It's cute.
I went shopping at a convenience store with my dad and my daughter.
Oh, my face.
Don't use it as a mirror.
There was a mirror.
Oh, well, well, well...
There's something wrong with it.
This way.
Maybe it's not really on.
You put it on like this, right?
Yeah. - Yeah.
Right, like this.
You don't put it on?
I see.
I was wrong.
The correct answer is a slap.
Can I ask him to try it again?
No, he might like this one.
What's with the stupid girl thing all of a sudden?
She's making it up.
They're all the rage.
It makes your legs look thinner.
He's bald.
You can take these off on hot days.
You don't have to wear it on cold days.
But you can do that, too, can't you?
Yes, you can.
Wearing them like this is all the rage right now.
Hmmm...
Karen, you have no idea. It's like a blistering hot mess.
You just gave me that impression.
I'm kind of on the bandwagon.
Like, yeah, yeah.
Secondhand clothes.
Vintage clothes.
Oh, you're wearing it.
Are you doing it? Like that.
It's not Goodwill.
There's a lot of used clothes here.
It's cute.
Yes, it is.
There's also a lot of figurines.
They're fashionable.
Fashionable.
This one's really cute, too.
I've never seen anything like it.
Accessories
Stylish.
Medicine?
Cute.
Is that right?
That one?
You know, the kind you take off the back and put around your neck?
I think so.
I like it.
It looks good.
The image of your forehead was too strong.
I'm not sure what to make of it.
I guess that's the way it should be.
Is it kind?
What's with that face?
I don't like it.
I have a lot of accessories.
Oh, my God! There's chicken!
What is this?
Food samples?
Fried chicken?
Chicken on the bone!
Oh, my God! That's interesting.
I'm a little excited.It makes me a little bit excited.
I love food samples, don't you?
Abandonment.
It says "waiver of duty.
This will be the doctor's snack.
Let's do it tomorrow.
Let's be silly.
Shanimony.
If you like that Mr. Tork...
Asumori's guess is positive about Shanimoni.
It's nice.
Cute
Yes, there are a lot of Trender's things.
That's right.
It's great.
It's full of stuff.
This is fun.
I don't know.
Well, now that I've had a chance to look around...
There are so many cute items here, from clothes to accessories.
From here on out, we'll be having a coordination showdown.
Today, I'd like to set a rule and have a coordination showdown.
We're going to have a blindfolded coordination showdown.
We're going to blindfold one person at a time.
We're going to blindfold each of you, and have you go to Spinz and make a coordinated outfit.
Sounds fun.
Okay, let's have Karen go around the store blindfolded first.
Whoever you want.
We're really going to get ready for this.
I've always wondered what it was like to be an idol.
Isn't this what an expedition is all about?
You're right. No suits, right?
That's right.
Right or left? Left.
What?
Can I have them put them on then?
It's either one or the other.
Isn't it cool?
It looks good on you.
Try it on and look cool.
Karen looks like this when she's tired.
Please don't tell me the truth.
When I'm tired, my eyes are all busted up like this.
You can't even see them now?
No, I can't.
Well, let's start with Karen's coordination.
You can guide her, or at least support her so she doesn't bump into you.
Do you have a theme in mind?
Yes, but Spinz has some cute items.
There's a kind of minefield-esque cuteness to them.
So I'd like to wear a collar with that kind of thing.
I'd like to wear a collar and accessories to make it look cute.
I'll see if I can find it.
I'm sure you're right. I'll do my best.
Karen, what should we start with?
I saw a little long one-piece bunny dress earlier.
So I went to look for it.
What about this?
What's this?
Are these the pants with holes in them?
I wonder if there's a hole.
There's no holes.
That's not quite right.
Not these.
You're looking for a dress.
I'm looking for a bunny dress.
Oh, I found something.
A bag?
What if there's a bag?
This way?
There's a poke-in here.
Mr. Money, he's a little strong.
I'm afraid to look.
Oh, here, what's this?
What? Where is it?
Eh, the bag is already there.
What are you doing?
I was just coming in with my hands outstretched.
It's not the bottom line.
Oh, wow.
I wonder what this is.
Let's try this one.
It's a different restaurant.
Oh, no!
What a surprise.
Surprise! Surprise!
Surprise, surprise, goodness.
I mean, this is really cool, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
What?
This one?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This one, right, bunny?
This one then.
Here you go.
I'll find a skelly for my bunny.
No, I'm still doing this with spin.
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh, this, this is a hat!Oh, this, this is a hat!
Oh, but the cat one was cute, too.
You are a cat.
This, oh, this!
This one! A collar!
What color is this?
How many colors do you think I have?
White.
I have two of them, both of them, and this one is a cat's hat, Gary.
I'll put this in the toolbox.
And arm covers... for your legs... for your legs... what do you call them?
Neat cover? Neat cover? I think I'll wear pants.
I give up then.
I give up. I think it'll make my legs thinner.
I'll put these on.
Are you sure?
Do this.
I'll take care of it. And I'll pick out a necklace.
I see.
Wow! There are ribbon ones, too, right?
The one you just put on.
You remember.
It's around here, right?
This one!
Is that it?
It came off.
Is it okay?
It's off.
It came off.
I'm sorry, it came off.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Not at all.
You can't say that with your face?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I told you I was against it.
You look like you're kidding.
I disagree.
Are you sorry?
I'm sorry.
You got it, didn't you?
I'm so sorry.
Your eyes are shattered.
That's it.
Is this the finish?
Yes, sir.
That's all.
Next, we'll coordinate Ms. Kitami.
Let's call her.
Let's go, Kitami-san.
She's cute.
So cute!
She's a tomboy.
She's like a beloved character.
I'll love her.
Don't laugh, Kitami-san.
Don't laugh.
Let's start.
What?
This one is better?
This one is better!
Do you have a particular eye you like to look at?
I saw the first one.
The long hat.
A hat! Oh!
Oh!
Aah! Oh!
A chair!
I know, I know!
I know it!
You saw it, right here!
I saw it! I saw it!
Oh! I see it! A chair!
Aah!
Aah! Up there!
Up there!
Aah! Oh, my God!
The floor!
Ah! There it is!
This is it!
That's it!
Oh!
Isn't this just what you wanted?
Oh, my God!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I know what I'm looking for.
Oh, my God!
That's great!
One time, you know, just passing through.
Oh, yeah.
Oh! Maybe it's around here.
Oh!
What? Is this it?
What are you after?
I saw a khaki bag.
I think I found it here.I think I found it here.
Khaki bag?
Oh, yeah!
We got this one and this one, right?
Oh! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Once we get this one.
Ah! Here it comes! Here it comes!
Oh, my God!
There it is! I think I'll take that one.
I'll take that one.
I want that one.
I got that one.
You want it?
I saw it in the men's section.
I want the pince-nez ones.
I'll go look for tops.
What's that?
That's a side camera.
Excuse me!
What? I don't know.
Maybe this is it.
There are so many of these shapes, right?
I'm sure.
This one. I don't know.
What are you doing?
What's with that move?
It's a fashion item, if you have it.
Yes, it is.
It's very fashionable.
Wow!
I want your hands.
I want hands.
Arm cover.
This is the red cover.
I don't know which one I want.
I mean, there's different colors and stuff.
I have no idea.
If I had the right hat, I would have picked the one with the border.
I want the striped one.
I don't know which one.
Striped.
I remember it was on this side.
I just don't know which one's on this side.
This one?
With blue eyes.
That pisses me off.
This one?
But this is what sells, right?
That's what I'm talking about.
What if it's not?
Well, well, well.
Okay, this one.
And you didn't buy the bottom one, did you?
If I don't buy this, it'll be a bread market.
Oh, no.
You never know what's going to happen.
You're right.
Color matters, right?
I'll buy this one.
I'll go with this one.
Are you finished?
Done.
Understood.
Ms. Kinoue's coordination is finished.
Okay, let's start with Ms. Kanel.
I'd like to have her try on the dress first.
I'm looking forward to it.
Then, please get dressed.
I'm off.
It looks like Ms. Kanell has finished changing.
I heard her laughing just now.
Let's have Ms. Kanell come in.
Canel-san, please.
Yes, ma'am.
me.
Wow!
This is a big traffic jam...
Oh, it's totally fine!
And that towel...
These are, um...
They're socks, but... yes, you bought socks, right? The pants are longer than I thought...
I can't see them, so...
You're enjoying fashion so much that you've become so flexible that you can wear it around your neck.
Excellent, excellent, excellent, excellent, excellent.
Yes, it's a necklace, thank you very much.
I was surprised. I thought it was the cat's star.
I thought it was a cat star.
This one, the cat one. I want this one.
I wanted this one, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one.
This is what I'm aiming for This is what I'm aiming for This is what I'm aiming for This is what I'm aiming for This is what I'm aiming for
That's what I was aiming for.
Then let's go to Rinne.
Now that Kitami's finished changing, let's have her make an appearance.
Let's have Kitami-san, please.
Kitami-san, please. So cute!
So cute!
Isn't it nice?
It's good, right?
I'm glad I got the one I wanted.I'm glad I got the one I wanted.
Everything is the same!
The goggles were the same color as yesterday.
You succeeded in choosing between the two.
That's right.
They were yellow.
There was yellow.
Here! This!
That was amazing.
You guessed it.
It's just a hunch, really.
It's the one I wanted.
Say it's the popular one.
I see you put your arms and head together.
I'm glad.
Same.
This is the one I wanted, too.
I was so surprised, wasn't I?
And the boots, too.
I'm glad you got the right size.
They fit perfectly.
It's all done.
They look like brothers.
I finished coordinating the two of them, but...
I asked the sales clerk at Spinz
how the two of them coordinated.
I'm sure he's curious.
I'm sure you're curious, aren't you?
I'd like to get some comments from them.
We finished coordinating today.
What do you think?
Well, they both have their own personalities.
It's great.
Yay!
It's usually when they're weird, you know?
No, no, no, no, no.
That's not what I meant.
It's totally fine if you take it positively.
Tachibana-san's border is a triple.
Both halves
That's a very high level.
That's for sure.
You are good at rice.
It's a very high level.
It's hard for me to do.
You're a pro.
I was making fun of you for a minute.
I've been tinkering with it.
It's hard.
How about you, Mr. Tani?
I really don't care if I dress the mannequins.
I think it's a perfect coordination.
And the way you put the goggles on.
Is it okay?
I gave it a score of 185.
What's the perfect score?
That's great.
So, I went to Spin's
I had a showdown with Mr. Spins!
Yay!
It's a full-fledged coordinate showdown!
It was fun!
It was fun.
What do you think?
Spinz has so many different kinds of clothes.
Even if they were, that's a lot of stuff.
And it's a lot of lectro combinations.
Spinz doesn't specialize in borders.
Even with blinders on, there's a lot of variation.
It was fun.
I thought the possibilities were endless
I thought the possibilities are endless.
I hope you all enjoy the coordination.
I hope you all have a lot of fun coordinating your outfits!
I hope all of you Italian guys will come to the concert
I want you to come to the concert with this set.
It's not bad.
On the contrary...
How was it, Rinne?
I was really going for it.
My memory's not what it used to be.
It was more fun.
There were so many things to choose from.
I actually chose a lot more than I thought I would.
That's why I want to do it again.
I want to do it again.
It was fun.
That's how we had the coordinate showdown.
Thank you very much.
We have a lot of other products, so I hope you all enjoy them!
Bill is located on the 2nd floor, so please come and visit us!
Thank you very much for joining us today! See you soon!